# Kim McCaskill

# Software Developer

## **SUMMARY**

I am a Software Developer passionate in problem-solving, user-centric design, and self growth. My 3 years in Hospitality Management allow me to resolve diverse business challenges with small and large teams. I have strengths in making conceptual transfers to learn new languages through Music Education.

Denver, CO

(904) 907-3277

kimmccaskill92@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/kimmccaskill/



github.com/kimmccaskill

kimmccaskill.com/

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Turing School of Software and Design** — *Student*

Sept 2019 - Apr 2020

- Turing students invest seven months in becoming job-ready software developers through sprint-style project-centric courses
- Focus on JavaScript fundamentals as well as 12 week focus learning React with 7 weeks dedicated to back-end concepts such as Node with Express

# **Grand Hyatt** — Operations Assistant Manager

July 2018 - Sept 2019

- Accomplished YoY productivity increase(~2%) across operational departments by analyzing labor standards
- Filled in as acting manager for short staffed departments of 8-20 employees
- Managed logistics of housekeepers in 514 room property
- Plan and coordinate events for 10-150 attendees

# **Chick-fil-A** — Director/Corporate Trainer

July 2016 - July 2018

- Onboarded 50+ team members in low-retention college store location
- Coordinated and implemented training workshops for leadership
- Worked with team of 80-100 to run efficient(chainwide 20%)
  Drive-Thru operations

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Front-End Development**

Turing School of Software and Design
Sept 2019 - Apr 2020

# **Instrumental Music Education**

Florida State University

Aug 2013 - Apr 2016

#### SKILLS/LANGUAGES

JavaScript

**ReactJs** 

Redux

NodeIs

React Native

CSS/Sass

Jest/Enzyme/Cypress

#### **PROJECTS**

# **Hangry Ateball**

github.com/hangry-ateball/hangry-a teball-fe

Find restaurants in your area that you can open in map app or share with friends via text.

React Native | Cypress

#### TicketCloud

github.com/kimmccaskill/tickets ticketcloud.herokuapp.com/

Utilizes TicketMaster's API to provide users with upcoming event ticket sale dates.

Week Sprint

React | Redux | Jest | Enzyme

## BluciferBNB

github.com/kimmccaskill/bnb

Bed & Breakfast app that houses data about different areas of Denver and associated rentals available in those areas.

React | React Router | Jest